https://mauiwine.com/policies/privacy/

Skip to contentPrivacy PolicyWe are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.We respect your right to privacy and will protect it; any information you provide is strictly confidential and solely for our company use. No information will be sold or shared with any other companies or organizations.If at any time you prefer not to be included in our mailings, please notify us by emailing us at info@mauiwine.com or call us at the winery and we will honor your request immediately +1 (808) 878-6058.Tedeschi Vineyards, Ltd. takes pride in only using the information online for your purchases. We do not share, sell, or distribute any information of any kind to anyone.Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.Security PolicyYour payment and personal information is always safe. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read over the internet.Connect with UsJoin Our Mailing List
Contact info
Address
14815 Piilani Hwy, Kula, HI 96790
Mailing
HC 1 Box 953, Kula, HI 96790
+1 (808) 878-6058
Wednesday–Sunday
11 am–5 pm Sub menuHomeVisitingThe ExperienceInteractive MapWine ClubFAQsOur WinesShopShipping PolicyDistributorsDownloadsBrandingHeritageOur StoryHappeningsContact Us
Get Directions Navigate using:Google Maps (Andriod/iOS) Apple Maps (iOS) Tasting Room 11 am–5 pm, Wednesday–Sunday 14815 Piilani Hwy, Kula, HI 96790 20.6481253, -156.3997033 WE'RE OPEN!Book your table in the King’s Cottage Tasting Room offering wine by the glass, wine flights, and wine cocktails. 11 am-5 pm, Wednesday-Sunday. Seated service only, no standing or bar. There is not a set price for wine tasting and no payment is required to book a reservation. Once seated, you will order from our wine menu as you wish. CLICK HERE TO RESERVE READ MORE AND SEE OUR MENUThe tasting room opens at 11 am and we take reservations up to 4 pm, which allows time for guests to enjoy themselves before we close at 5 pm. Seating ends at 4 pm. Last call for drink and winery food purchase is 4:30 pm. We strongly encourage you to make a reservation.PLEASE NOTE:We are not operating tours.We are not hosting groups over 6 people.Face coverings are required unless seated at a table.Our property is only accessible to seated guests of MauiWine.We do not have public restrooms, restrooms are for seated guests only.Guests can shop the winery boutique without a reservation. There is no wine tasting allowed in the boutique.
CLOSE
